Jomar Oliver Reyes

IT Support Specialist

ADDRESS Langfeldstr. 35, Erlangen 91058,

Germany

EMAIL jomaroliverreyes@gmail.com

NATIONALITY Filipino

PHONE +49 1747827269

DATE OF BIRTH 24.09.1987



Profile

I'm an experienced IT person who is passionate about technical support, maintenance, administration, and management that has a strong background in these aspects. A self-motivated and self-taught learner with a few experiences in web designing and development.

Employment History

April 2018 — June 2020

PHILIPPINES AND HONGKONG

IT Systems Engineer

Velocity Solutions, Inc.

Responsible for assisting/resolving the clients' requests & issues on Windows/Mac/Linux desktops, laptops, and servers thru remote and virtual environments. Setup, implement, manage and monitor IT Systems & Infrastructure.

Dec 2015 - Dec 2017

RIYADH, SAUDI ARABIA

IT Support Specialist

Wallan Trading Co. / Wallan Maintenance Co.

Responsible for providing L1/L2 technical support via telephone, email, tickets, and remote desktop. Deploying, maintaining, troubleshooting, and resolving a wide range of software, hardware, and network issues.

June 2013 - July 2015

JEDDAH, SAUDI ARABIA

IT Support Specialist

GAMA Services LTD. and KAMCJ Hospital

Responsible for deploying, configuring, managing, maintaining, and monitoring the IT systems and network infrastructure of a contractual company and for the hospital as their client and providing a daily technical support and assistance routine.

April 2012 - Oct 2012

MAKATI, PHILIPPINES

IT System & Network Administrator

Torch Film Productions Studios, Inc.

Responsible for day-to-day operations and administration of IT Infrastructure. Securing the systems, business applications, and maintaining network stability.

Nov 2007 — April 2012 MAKATI, PHILIPPINES

IT Support Engineer

Imaginary Friends Studio, Inc.

Responsible for providing technical support to the users. Setup, configure new machines and maintain IT Systems, Network Infrastructure, and provide hands-on training for the users.

Education

May 2017 - 2022

AMA University and Colleges

QUEZON CITY, PHILIPPINES

Bachelor of Science in Information Technology

Major in Software Engineering and Web Application Development

April 2005 — May 2007 PARANAQUE, PHILIPPINES Asian Institute of Computer Studies

Associate degree in Computer Technology

Major in Computer Programming, Systems and Network Management

March 2001 - May 2005

Pasay City South High School

PARANAQUE, PHILIPPINES High School Student

Skills

Cloud Computing & Virtualization

Software & Hardware Installation

Troubleshooting & Maintenance

Microsoft Office & Adobe Apps

System & Network Administration

Web Design & Development

Languages

Tagalog

English

Arabic

German

• • • •

Hobbies

Reading and studying about technology, watching movies on Netflix, listening to music, playing computer/mobile games, and basketball with friends.

16.05.2022